{
    "subject": "Rex_Balsom",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Jennifer_Rappaport",
    "human_readable": "Rex Balsom is married to Jennifer Rappaport.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9284684062004089,
            "question": "Can you describe the relationship between Rex Balsom and Jennifer Rappaport?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9250966310501099,
            "question": "Who is Rex Balsom married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8846035599708557,
            "question": "Who is married to Jennifer Rappaport?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8794140815734863,
            "question": "Does Rex Balsom have a wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6938579678535461,
            "question": "Is Rex Balsom in a relationship?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6879258155822754,
            "question": "What is the name of Jennifer Rappaport's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6678411364555359,
            "question": "What is the name of Jennifer Rappaport's husband?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.553139865398407,
            "question": "What is Jennifer Rappaport's marital status?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36849644780158997,
            "question": "Is Rex Balsom single?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.17683817446231842,
            "question": "Who are the spouses in this relationship?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Rex Balsom is married to Jennifer Rappaport.",
            "html": "yago_25788_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Rex Balsom single?",
            "html": "yago_25788_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Jennifer Rappaport's marital status?",
            "html": "yago_25788_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Jennifer Rappaport's husband?",
            "html": "yago_25788_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25788_113.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25788_119.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25788_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25788_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25788_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25788_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25788_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25788_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25788_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25788_70.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe context information indicates that Jennifer Rappaport and Rex Balsom had a marriage, although it was annulled. The documents mention their elopement in the summer of 2003 and subsequent divorce when Jen (Jennifer) married Joey Buchanan in August of the same year. Thus, the statement \"Rex Balsom is married to Jennifer Rappaport\" can be considered correct based on the provided context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "multiple sources state their marriage was short-lived and annulled due to Jen's affair with Joey Buchanan.",
            "category": 0
        }
    }
}